I'm going to click this button right here.
And this button.
And then I'm going to click this button.
I'm kidding.
Man, look at this right here.
Organization.
I'm actually so happy I spent a lot of time doing that.
This just brings a joy of cheer to my eye.
That made no sense what I just said.
A tear of joy from my eye.
English is not my first language, apparently.
Okay, I did all that.
But I'm not done.
Because I was about to do other things.
People are slowly moving in again.
That's good.
Maurice.
I see your eyeball in the mini shark.
You really don't want to know how it was made.
Out of shark children?
By the way, I already have a mini shark, but I guess you wouldn't know that because I bought this from Dante.
And you're not him.
You are not him.
Okay, so look at this inventory right here.
You see something special about it?
It's empty.
And that means it's time to fill it up.
But with items from the underground, because I want to go exploring, I need to go inside some caves and fuck some shit up, if you know what I mean.
I really, really need to do that.
I have an itch to kill things and get loot and explore things and shoot.
But wait, hold on.
Before we do that, let me quickly... I have to rename these chests as well.
Weapons.
And this one is also weapons.
Whoops, jump.
This one shall be weapons.
These are armors.
Oh, I need to test something.
Let's say I remove this.
I put it here now.
It's still called armor.
Perfect.
That's all I needed to know.
Great.
Because otherwise I'd have to redo the naming later.
And I don't know if I want to do that.
So let's just do that now.
Armor.
And armor.
And then over here we have accessories.
Hopefully I spelled that right.
Accessories.
Like that.
And accessories.
Man, I'm so happy there's no enemies while I'm doing this.
That makes me happy.
Put this torch back, please.
There we go.
There's also accessories.
Is it with two S's?
Hold on.
Accessories.
No, that looks wrong to me.
Honestly, I don't know any grammatical rules.
Not even in Danish.
All the rules I follow or does it look right or does it look wrong, you know?
So far it's done me okay, I think.
This is probably gonna sound really stupid if I'm actually misspelling this right now.
But yeah.
Then we have vanity.
Maybe we don't need this many chests for vanity.
Or maybe we do, I don't know.
Vanity.
Probably that... you know what?
We probably do, because there's a shit ton of vanity items and I kind of... a part of me likes hoarding items you've probably noticed.
I do like to hoard and collect things.
I have the same issue in real life where if I buy something, the box it comes in, I keep it forever.
Just in case, you know... wait, did I write variety?
Vanity.
Did I write it wrong on all of them?
No, I'm good.
Now this one.
This is materials.
Rich... oh my god, I have to rename that every time.
Materials.
And materials here as well.
And that one.
I guess materials is gonna be a big one here.
I'm gonna have a lot of them.
I have intentions of putting appropriate chest styles for each of these different categories.
And then we have this one which is...
I don't know what you would call this.
I'm tempted to write miscellaneous.
But that's dangerous.
But miscellaneous and the fact that I simply don't...
I'm not able to categorize it anywhere else for now.
Okay, this is fine there.
This right here actually has nothing yet.
This is easy.
That's potions.
This one is also potions.
And then we... this one over here is ingredients for potions.
So I guess... I don't know what you call that.
I guess potion ingredients.
That makes a lot of sense.
Very descriptive.
If I mouse over that, I'll know what it means.
Ores and doors.
Not just ores.
And this right here... I'm not sure what this is yet.
I know that this one I want to put it one...
Whoops, not there.
Put it here.
This is also ores.
Ores.
Okay, this is fish.
Fishing.
I want to say the right side here is... yeah, that's food.
Good.
This is also fishing.
And we have one more for food.
Maybe I'll have a separate chest just for bait.
I'm not sure yet.
I haven't decided.
Whoops.
I keep removing these torches by accident.
This one is construction.
All of these are really...
Actually, this is more like blocks.
Yeah, this side is going to be blocks and this is construction.
Nice.
Very good, very good.
And then we have more blocks.
Cool.
All right.
So far, so good.
Let's... oh, Jeff!
You are here.
That's perfect.
Well, I put you here, didn't I?
So...
I wonder why my predecessor spontaneously burst into flames.
Hopefully it doesn't happen to me.
Yeah, it was me.
I did it.
And I don't regret a thing.
Hold on.
I actually need to ask you about something here.
Materials.
No, accessories.
I have some new items that I want to show this guy.
I want to try these.
I need to remind myself what that is.
Let me see.
What else have I not tried yet?
Let's remind myself of that.
The Magma Stone, actually.
This one I also want to check again.
This one I want to check again.
This is a material.
Maybe I'll check the watch again.
What else?
What else new did I get?
Nassar.
Wait, Frogleg?
And let me check these, actually.
Probably I can combine this.
Wait, double jump?
Oh, I already have one of these, so I'm gonna sell that.
Sort this.
Perfect.
Jeff, where'd you go?
Jeff, my man.
What about the Frogleg?
Sailfish boots and Frogleg.
So frog webbing, I already have.
So what about the Frog webbing here?
Oh, frog gear.
I need a flipper for that.
Don't have that.
Okay, let's wait with that then.
Now, this watch right here, I can combine with a depth meter.
I have a compass.
I don't think I have that.
Oops.
Get out of here.
Glue slime.
I was talking to Jeff.
So rude.
Oh, Jeff is wandering back inside of here.
He's not supposed to do that.
Okay, then we have this one.
Medicated bandage.
Hey, I can make this.
Let's put that there for now.
Then we have this one.
Manaf... Oh, didn't I already make this actually?
Star cloak?
Wait,
I turned my mana flower into this one.
Jagged magnet flower.
Automatically use mana potions when needed.
Right, so instead of manually using mana potions having this on, it gave me a bunch of mana potions.
Speaking of mana potions, I should actually just have them on me.
Like, these are the items here.
Maybe not the wood, but all of these up here are items that I always want on my bar.
You know?
And then I want other items such as healing potions, of course.
For this one.
And I want mana.
So lesser... no, just normal.
Just normal.
And then I'm gonna do that to these, so that they stay.
And now, before I forget, let me go grab the
bezewar, because we can use that to combine them.
Okay, let's do that right now.
Let's actually just combine all the things we can combine.
I probably should take this with me and put it somewhere else.
The tinkerer's workshop, I think it needs to be in the main storage facility.
Okay, storage facility, put it... oh yeah, we made a new space here.
The medicated bandage is also a material, so we can further use this in other recipes.
Nice.
That's done.
Okay, Jeff, I'm not done with you.
Where did you go to?
Jeff, what about this magma stone?
A fire gauntlet.
Increases melee knockback and melee attacks inflict fire damage.
Cool.
But I'm not going for a melee, so...
molten quiver increases arrow damage by 10% and greatly increases arrow speed.
Yo, that seems kind of sick, actually.
I mean, if you're rocking bow and arrow, of course.
Not bad.
That's nice.
I really like that.
The plan.
We need a fast clock.
I guess, to make a fast clock, you need a watch?
No, apparently you don't.
I need something else.
What about these?
Okay, this is just kind of useless, actually.
I already have this stuff.
So these can also be sold.
This one, I kind of want to put there again.
Let me actually...
let me see here.
This one is a must, I feel like.
This one is not a must.
What does this do again?
Immunity to knockback and fire blocks and two defense.
Wait, this is actually a material.
Jeff, please tell me what I can do with this.
Ang shield.
Most debuffs.
That's pretty sick.
My guess is I'm gonna get this from the desert biome.
The Ang.
Sounds like something out of Egypt or something, right?
Maybe from that temple on the ground that I don't know how to access.
That's probably what's going on there.
But immunity to knockback, I don't know if I...
Do I get knocked back a lot?
I'm not actually sure.
Maybe I do.
And this one, let me just check the other ones here.
There was the bee cloak and the star veil.
Increases length of invincibility after taking damage.
Also kind of cool, but I don't have a cross necklace, so can't do much there.
The mana flower?
I'm not actually sure where I got that at first.
Did I just use a mana potion?
Maybe.
Oh my god.
Well, there it is.
That's how I got it.
Perfect.
I'm actually gonna make another one.
Accessories.
Because look at this, I should have a rash nature skip.
Let me do that as well.
Now that I finally have my inventory sorted, I feel like it's so much easier to have this overview of what's going on.
Oh wait, I need to combine them over there.
Really quickly.
Abigail?
Oh no, you heal.
I wonder...
What?
I can't do any more for you without plastic surgery?
What the hell are you talking about?
Oh well.
Well, hi there, mortal.
What can I do for you today?
Okay, this guy has lost his mind.
Completely.
Wait, he sells greater mana potions.
I can just buy a bunch.
A hundred...
Why am I not just buying a shit ton of these?
Isn't that amazing?
Has a chance to record songs.
There are so many obscure items in this game.
Like, what does that even mean?
Has a chance to record songs.
Huh?
Equipable as well.
So interesting.
Oh yeah, I wanted to sell.
Buy this one and that one.
And that's good.
Let's go combine.
Let's make the mana flower.
And mana cloak.
Wait a minute, stars restore mana when collected.
Is that actually better than what I have?
Increases pickup range for mana stars.
I feel like that is better.
Right?
It causes stars to fall after taking damage.
But then again, when you take damage, the stars fall and then those stars restore mana.
Yeah, I mean, I'll try it.
Wild mana cloak.
Hmm.
Let's rock that for a bit.
This also automatically uses mana potions.
Okay.
Has the same amount of reduced mana cost.
That's nice.
Wait, I can have both maybe.
Wait a minute, does that stack?
Wait a minute.
Uses five mana?
Oh my god!
Hold on.
I need a better test weapon here for this.
I think it does stack.
I think it stacks, dude.
Oh wait, I put this magic stuff up here.
Actually, I should write that.
Magic weapons.
This one in the center is ranged weapons.
And then we have melee weapons.
Melee weapons.
Let's see here.
So this one costs.
Oh, this is also a small one.
Let's do this one.
Masterful magic missile.
This is the best in slot.
I actually need to carry this.
Uses 10 mana.
Then I equip this.
Nine mana.
Eight mana.
Nice!
Nice.
That's actually pretty big.
But then again, this one is kind of a must, right?
So, yeah.
I guess I have to choose.
For now, I'm gonna wear the... Oh, actually!
I have an actual cloak on right now.
Look!
Oh, I'm definitely wearing the cloak then.
Just for the looks.
Bro, hell yeah.
That's decided right there.
Easy decision.
I was torn, but now I'm not.
Okay, put this stuff back in.
Actually, keep this here for now.
And then all this goes back in here.
Go back in.
The magic missile.
Let's put that... hold on, 37...
51 damage now.
Yeah.
I think it's nice to have this knife.
Also, it says Inflic Shadow Flame on hit.
I gotta pay attention to what exactly that means.
Is this some kind of fire that can't be put out or something?
That's what I imagine.
Now, this mana potion here, I don't really need to carry that, I guess.
Actually, I can do this and save this one for big enemies.
You know, for smaller excursions, the normal mana potion is probably preferable.
And the laser rifle.
I don't think I want to carry that around.
Does that count as magic?
I guess it does, right?
That would go in here then.
It's a bit unintuitive, but... You know what?
I could try this.
The mythical flower.
Let's try rocking that for a bit.
Because that's a lot of damage.
And 25% critical.
And it has quite a fast range, like rate of fire.
And they bounce around as well, so not bad, right?
Sulphur butterfly.
Also bait.
Okay, so what else do I need for my expedition?
Actually, I changed my mind.
Put the mana potions back in.
Potions.
And the reason is, I need to fix my inventory.
The other thing I want to bring for my expedition is fishing equipment.
Because I want to do some fishing this time around.
We're going to be masturbating so hard today, dude.
Put this... I guess the bug net is not something that I... Actually, this one doesn't have to be there.
No, put that there.
That's fine.
This one wants to be there.
That one stays there.
And then we have the thing easily equipable.
Go in, sword items.
I guess the wood can also... Let me turn the wood into platforms, because that's always nice to have on you.
That's another item that's nice to have on you.
Make this.
Put the money in.
I actually have a lot of money.
I have two platinum, almost three platinum.
Pretty cool.
Actually, speaking of platinum, there's a...
There's an ore in this game called platinum.
I wonder if you actually...
If you can turn that into platinum money.
Wait a minute.
I actually got to test that real quick.
Don't I have... yeah, platinum bar?
I mean, platinum coins are presumably made from platinum.
Nope, I want to talk to Jeff.
Can I make money out of this?
Yeah, maybe that would be too broken to have my own mint.
Maybe this is what I'll need later on to make the clock.
Hold on.
Maybe there's other items here that are useful.
At some point, I have to put in all my ores again into Jeff.
I'm going to need to put my ores inside of Jeff and he will tell me all the possibilities that I have.
Maybe there's something I've forgotten, you know?
Okay, that's fine.
Platinum goes back then.
Okay, so fishing is taken care of.
Then I need to bring some potions as well.
And from now on, I'm going to be carrying my potions in my piggy bank.
Just for the sake of organization.
Sort this stuff.
Give me that.
So what do I want to bring?
I think Obsidian is always good to have.
I'm going to leave one of them here.
One regeneration.
One swiftness.
Actually, leave all of them except one in here.
I always want to have one in here so that I can auto-stack.
Like that.
Belunker is nice.
Wait, yeah, one there.
You know what?
This one could be nice.
I am tired of all the enemies that happen all the time, so if I can reduce that, perfect.
Water walking, archery, hunter.
This one could also be nice to bring.
Gravitation, not really.
Mining is nice.
I will be doing some of that.
Let's bring this one as well.
Crate potions, definitely.
Let's bring sonar as well.
We're going to be doing some fishing.
Recall, definitely.
Those are a must.
Leave them here.
And potion of return.
Sort these, and then open that one.
Inside of here, we're going to be storing all of these potions.
Except that one, because that's quite needed.
And then every time I need to buff, I just pull out my piggy bank and I, you know, easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
Now, I realize this storage facility here is not complete.
We're missing some walls, but that'll happen later.
I also want to predify it a little bit.
Honestly, predifying structures is kind of fun, you know?
Building.
I like doing that stuff.
Even though this took a long time to do, I kind of enjoyed the slow pace of it.
Is that crazy?
Okay, so now we have crate potions, we have fishing potions, we have bait, we have a mechanics rod.
We are freaking ready, I think.
Wait, wait, wait.
We need to bring one more thing.
Let's bring some keys.
That's something I always forget.
If I'm going to go also all the way down here, maybe I'll check this out today as well, all the way down there.
See what's going on down there now.
So these would be in the miscellaneous one.
Yes.
So a shadow key.
Let's keep that on us.
And what else?
I think that's the golden key.
Let's keep those two on us.
Put them in here, actually.
Like that.
They belong here.
Nice.
What else should I be needing for this journey?
I have my pickaxe.
Superior orichalcum pickaxe, by the way.
Kind of a sick one.
I really, really like it.
Potions, ingredients, ores, fishing is done, construction.
Let's see here.
There's nothing in here I should bring.
Vanity, no.
Accessory.
Is there any special accessory that I need to bring that I don't have on me?
I was considering trying this out again, by the way.
But no, it's too annoying to have the... I accidentally click that button all the time.
And I go in directions that I'm not intending to go.
Feels bad.
So it's time!
Let's go exploring!
Give me this.
Okay, the magic missile can kill things through a wall because of the AOE explosion.
How is the magic missile not the best thing ever?
Fantastic.
Man, I'm so glad I found that.
I feel like it's been carrying me a lot.
Okay, let's go find some more ore.
That's the number one priority.
I want to find titanium.
I want to find titanium and I want to find cobalt and orichalcum.
Let me go through a new... Let me actually go through this one this time.
I'm going to go to the jungle and then I'm going to go through this path I made and dig the rest of the way because I'm missing this part, it seems.
Let's do that.
Let's let go.
Man, I look so cool with the cape on now.
I look like a proper mage.
Oh, look at that!
The stars fell from the sky.
You saw that?
That did a lot of damage.
Hey, you like this?
You mad, bro?
There we go.
Taking care of.
Now, has anyone moved in in the desert home here at all?
Or what?
Why has nobody moved in here?
Hey, what are these guys even doing here?
The fuck are you doing here?
Get out of here, bastards!
All right, keep going.
Look at that, stars falling from the sky.
Man, it's so dark.
I'm taking so much damage here, just traversing.
Where is this spot?
Oh, it's all the way over there.
Okay, I thought it was there already.
Nevermind.
I've got to keep going.
What is this?
Oh, I'm getting a lot of fallen stars.
And if they give me mana, it's pretty nice.
I think I'm liking this cloak.
I think I like this cloak a lot.
Look at that background, by the way.
Rainbows and differently colored trees.
What a weird biome, huh?
Get out of here.
Oh yeah, I wanted to pay attention to the effect of Shadow Flame.
Let me try and see that now.
Oh yeah, they burn with a purple flame.
All right, that's like fire, but maybe better.
What about these guys?
They also burn.
Perfect.
Yeah, I should just be using this knife whenever I'm not in any really tight situations, because I want to save my mana for the hard situations.
Whoa!
A derpling!
Hello?
I don't know if I like that.
That's nasty.
Hey, oh no.
Oh, look at the way I'm sort of pushing him back.
That's nice.
Hello.
What the hell are you even?
Derpling.
There's so many of them.
Yeah, you like that?
They hate the magic.
Oh, a giant tort.
Whoa!
All right, this guy's not fucking around.
Got him.
Okay, this shit is dangerous.
I got to get down here.
Whoa, let's see what's here.
I need to chill for a second.
I have a low HP.
What's that?
A worm statue.
I want to delete that.
Wait, a meat grinder?
Huh?
Okay, another crafting station.
Cool.
Did I get that from, I guess, one of the kills I just did?
Why did I just do that?
Don't unleash.
Oh, we've got some stuff over here.
Also, here's the time.
Now, I got to be using... let's say I'm using Spelunker now.
I need to remind myself what exactly the colors correspond to.
This is Cobalt, for sure.
A giant, another one.
Man, look how tanky they are.
Everything is so difficult in this game.
Just suddenly.
Like, last time I had my ass handed to me.
That was some brutal shit.
Oh, kind of cool how the stars actually come down here.
I wasn't expecting that.
That's nice.
What's this over here?
Oh, it's lead.
But actually, I kind of need that too.
I feel like I'm running out of lead.
There are some things I wanted to build, like the wall actually.
Oh, what is the fuck?
An Arapaima!
And I'm dead.
My living streak was ended by Arapaima.
I wouldn't call that a streak.
Just saying.
Oh, it's a fish.
I thought it was some kind of fucked up worm creature.
Goddamn.
Open this real quick and deposit.
Also, look at this now.
If I click this button, this should be really nice.
Look, most things go in.
Beautiful.
That is the fruit of the labors.
Actually, instead of putting that there, put it in here.
If you leave some room, there will be room to put extra things in there.
Let's put the meat grinder over here.
I'm curious what that will do.
Grind meat, obviously.
But you know, what else?
What's up, Jeff?
Actually, Jeff, let me speak to you.
Help me.
I hear there's a woman out there well versed in fighting back the forces you just unleashed.
Maybe if you prove yourself, you can get her attention.
Yeah.
So I think... I think killing the wall of flesh unleashed these forces.
So who is this woman?
The tortured soul down in the underworld sure looks familiar.
Have you tried using purification powder on him?
No, I haven't.
I don't know who that is.
But now that you say it, let me go get some purification powder.
Uh, who was that?
Rosalva, where is she?
Is she even here?
She's all the way over there, of course.
Okay.
I'm actually going there.
Fuck it.
We go down here first.
Let me talk to you guys first.
I've got the cure for what else you get it, ale.
No, uh, that's a good one, dude.
What about you, mortal?
Do you sell anything new?
Oh, I never checked explosive powder with Jeff.
I need to do that.
Yep.
Explosive powder check.
What's that?
All right, let's head upstairs.
That's a failing.
It looked... Oh, wait a minute.
We've got stuff here.
It's, it's, it's everywhere.
It's actually everywhere.
Amazing.
Look, there's more there.
It just randomly spawned in anywhere in the world, it seems.
I wonder if there's this stuff in the underworld too.
Probably, right?
Precise depth meter.
Thank you.
Die.
Cool.
All right, let's go up.
Talk to Rousselba.
What was I getting again?
Oh yeah, purification powder.
Little, little, little, little, little, little.
Further up.
What's that?
Oh, it's lit.
I really need to make a better way of getting up here.
Teleporter, maybe.
Just run wires all the way up.
I guess I technically could do that.
It would just take a bit of time.
All right, Rousselba.
Uh, let me see.
What do you got?
You actually have new items.
Potted hello bamboo.
Cool.
Uh, I want this though.
Let me actually just have 160 of that.
I feel like it's something I should be maybe using.
Uh, that was a dolphin.
Maybe I'll just go down here.
Since I'm here anyway.
No, no, no.
I need to go collect my stuff.
Did I lose anything over here?
Two gold?
Nah, not worth going back for.
I'm gonna go down here.
Fuck it.
Right?
Just fuck it.
We go down here and we continue.
Maybe even dig through here all the way there.
That seems good to me.
And then we also utilize potions to see things.
Maybe I should have like protection potions on while I'm exploring because it's...
It's kind of difficult right now.
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm struggling.
So how about we do...
some... whoops, get away from me.
Where's my iron skin?
Don't I have that?
Let's do a hunter potion so we can see the enemies.
Invisibility.
So less enemies.
And... oh my gosh, get away.
Let's get, uh...
I don't know what else to use.
It's flunker, right.
I need to make more of that, by the way.
What is that?
Is that what I think it is?
Oh, it's tin, never mind.
I thought it was titanium.
That is...
You know what's funny about the stars coming down?
It's easy to see when I take damage.
You know, when the stars are falling, I've taken damage.
What is that?
A strange plant.
Can be traded for rare dyes.
All right.
Hold on, I can actually...
Tin.
Yeah, I should be using the map for this.
What have we got here?
I'm not sure this is anything useful.
We've got cobalt here.
No, I'm not gonna take that.
I want to find the good stuff.
There, or recalcum.
There's a bat bat over there.
I'll take the bat bat.
But first...
Ah, don't you...
Oh my god.
There we go.
Look at that guy.
Also, I should be wearing this, I think.
No, I should be drinking the potion.
I need my protection on me.
Drink mining.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, baby.
That's what I'm talking about.
Let me grab this.
A bat bat.
Oh, there's oracalcum right there.
But what I really want is titanium.
Zoom.
Further down.
What's that?
Ah, cool.
What do we have?
Not seeing anything.
Actually, I forgot what the titanium looked like.
It's not that.
That's platinum.
Want the lomi titanium?
Come on, let me check.
No, that's tin.
Fuck.
I believed...
Oh, this one, maybe.
No, that's platinum.
I believe it was very sparkly and very colorful last time.
That's like very jemmy.
A jungle creeper.
Oh, wow.
That did a lot of damage.
Yeah, don't hit me.
Missed.
Very good, very good.
There's a moss hornet there.
This is treacherous terrain.
What's that over there?
Man, I'm using a lot of time killing enemies when I want to be mining.
What's this again?
Oh, it's crinting.
What is this platinum?
I just need to see it one more time, and then I'll always remember what it looks like.
Definitely.
That's it, I think.
That's it right there.
I found it.
I have found...
This is 100% titanium.
Look how sparkly it is.
Yeah, look.
Beautiful.
Okay, great.
I've looted that already.
It looks so violent whenever these stars are falling.
Something in the water.
Oh, it's just a loot thingy.
I will be taking this Orykalkon, please.
It is mine.
Oh no, the potion wore off.
I need it.
I absolutely need to have this potion on.
I need to make more.
Okay, let's try and focus on mining now.
No fighting, just mining.
In fact, I'm gonna put this on as well.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Wait, what?
Why can't I...
Hello?
Why can't I destroy this?
The hell is that?
What?
Don't I have a crazy...
Hold on.
Clorified!
Aha!
How do I mine that?
Hello?
Interesting.
All right, now I know what that looks like.
Look how fast I'm mining.
It's insane.
Okay.
Come on, show me the goods.
Show me the titanium.
And hold the arrow.
Whoop!
I was stuck just now.
Just stick down.
Oh yeah, this is...
I can't go through that.
I can't even see what's happening.
This is so funny.
I am taking this.
There it is.
I see some over there on the right.
This is funny, man.
Just the speed at which I'm mining is just absolutely bonkers.
Give me all of this.
Holy crap.
Further down.
That's how I escape enemies.
Just dig.
Get out of there.
Show me some more.
Look, I just escaped that guy just by digging.
Oh god, that's an enemy.
I'm actually soon dead.
Oh, what is hitting me?
What did I take damage from?
Stinger.
I have no idea where you were, dude.
I didn't even see you.
Was it this guy?
No, that's a moss hornet.
Huh?
Didn't even see the guy.
Okay, now we click this amazing button.
Most things go away.
Now, I want a bit of silt inside the ores such that it can also be sorted.
Let's do one in here, like that.
Banner.
Delete it.
The unholy arrow.
Let's put the arrows over here somewhere.
Ranged weapons.
Ammo for ranged weapons.
That makes sense to me.
Moon glow.
I guess I didn't have any of this.
So I'm going to put one of them in here so that we can stack them later.
The strange plant.
Let's put that there for now.
And the silt.
We can use that immediately.
I forgot about the other things where you can put in this.
Let me check.
Silt slash fossil piles.
Okay, gotcha.
Everything in.
Oh, I already love this new system of mine.
It's so good.
Okay, I think the best way back is to teleport.
Let's do it.
Oh, wait.
It's over here.
Put me at this place, and then we're almost back.
Perfect.
Let's go collect the money.
If we even had some.
Oh, I forgot to make spelunker potions.
It's all right.
We'll do it the old-fashioned way.
The problem is now I have to get used to the different colors now for the ores when I don't have the potion on me.
Or activate it.
They look a little different.
I don't fucking know what this is.
Platinum, okay.
That's a biggie.
Holy shit.
Look how long that is.
The angry trap.
Oh, get away from me.
Oh my god, I'm actually dying already.
How is this real life?
Good thing stars don't fall when I just walk into vines or thorns.
That would be kind of annoying.
Oh, no, I want to be invisible.
Where is this?
Invisibility.
I guess we can put on the hunter one.
The hunter one is nice.
I get to at least see where the danger is.
I hate spiders.
Oh my god, the knockbag is terrible here.
This guy has a lot of HP.
Heal.
Oh, there's another one.
Holy fuck.
I can't really go anywhere.
I have so many enemies.
Like, are they respawning faster than I can kill them?
Is that what's happening here?
I can't catch a break.
I can't get down here.
There's too much shit.
I just got hit by something and I don't know what I got hit by.
There are so many projectiles that you almost can't see at all and it's so confusing.
Also, I'm suffering from something.
I'm poisoned.
Yeah, I need to wait here.
I need to wait here.
Get purified!
Purified!
Heal up.
Let's just chill.
Should've brought a campfire, I guess, or one of those healing things we can hang up.
This place is nuts.
Give me that money.
Is it dead?
Good.
How do I get past this shit?
What is this right here?
It's a bush.
While I regen, I'm just gonna mine a bit.
I guess we'll do it.
Uh-oh.
Heal.
There we go, he's dead.
Now it's your turn.
He's hitting me from a distance with a projectile that's impossible to see.
There we go.
Okay.
Nope, we're still not done.
I can't even face him, he's gonna insta-kill me.
Oh my god.
I'm so low HP.
Why is my regen so bad?
We gotta use a potion.
Regeneration potion.
Activate.
How much better is it?
It's a lot better, I guess.
It's not like, amazingly better.
Everything has respawned since I can't progress here.
I just don't have the weapons.
I don't have the damage to even do anything here.
It's insane.
I gotta dig my own tunnel.
I can't go through the caves.
Keep digging.
I can't see, but that's fine.
Just keep going.
Here we go.
Drainage time.
And all that.
Also be on the lookout for ores.
I don't see any right here.
Ah, that's OriCalcom for sure.
Cool.
Give me the lead.
Got more spiders down here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Is this the impenetrable it is?
The jungle creeper is a terrible foe.
I hate it.
At least it doesn't shoot projectiles.
That pleases me greatly.
What's this?
I believe that's cobalt.
Oh, wait, wait.
This right here.
That is titanium.
Yep.
It's very sparkly.
Actually not that hard to spot.
Very sparkly and finely grained, if that makes sense.
I'm doing pretty well finding this stuff, even when I'm not having the potion on me.
Also, let me get this green stuff.
Give me the green.
Okay, keep going down.
I cannot want...
What am I called?
What is this right here?
Rich mahogany?
Really?
Down here?
Interesting.
I love exploring the caves.
That's the best, actually.
Oops, shouldn't have done that.
We're fine.
No ores here.
Oh, I thought this guy was about to move through the...
Oh, this is...
I'm gonna kill you.
I will murder you.
Hold on, let me actually try the other weapon I have.
Oh, wait,
I should probably...
Let me hang like this.
Oh, dude!
It's a little harder to aim with, but if you hit them...
Okay, this little piece is annoying.
There we go.
Now I can do this.
This is not bad.
Like, if you can find a good angle here, this weapon is sort of sick.
And these things bounce around down there, right?
So just spam that shit right now.
Kill them all, burn them!
Kill it with fire!
Come on.
Yeah!
Yeah, that took a lot.
But I think I got them.
Amazing.
I'll take this.
I need to put this weapon here, because I think I like this.
This weapon right here in close quarters?
Very nice.
I'm a fan.
Oh,
no.
Oh, I can't see.
I can't see.
We're fine.
What did I just do?
How did I...
I somehow put down the void vault in my panic.
The panic void vault.
Oops, the daisy.
Hello.
Get out of here.
Nice.
Also, I should probably not have my chisel on, should I?
I probably should.
I'm doing a lot of digging.
What is this?
Oh, it's stone.
Why did it look like something else?
Just go further, further down.
Actually, I keep going the same route here.
What's that?
Ah, that's the thing I can't mine.
Ah, you know what?
I bet if I make a titanium pickaxe, I'll be able to do it.
That's like the next step, I think.
Am I seeing anything?
Hold on.
Any oars...
Actually, there's something red there.
Man, those projectiles they're shooting, I...
Fuck, it's insane.
You cannot see them, and they kill you.
Like, what am I getting hit by?
Hello?
What's hitting me?
I mean, I'm poisoned, but something else was hitting me just now.
Kill it.
Hate those guys.
Wait a minute, is that a trap over there?
What's that?
Oh, it's dynamite!
It's Dunamit.
I see you.
Fuck off.
Satisfying.
Who sets up these things?
That's what I want to know.
Okay, he's dead.
That's nice.
What is that?
A king statue?
Deleted.
Somebody wants statues.
But there's so many of these statues as well.
I feel like there's got to be something more to it, other than just...
They spawn certain enemies after a time.
And honestly, it does seem a little inconsistent as well.
Like, some of them do, some of them don't in a way.
Like, where nothing happens at all, it's a little bit weird.
Look at that!
Geometry.
Is he Orykalko?
Oh,
you've gone burned.
Oh, it doesn't have a lot of range, actually.
Like, it drops off quite...
Doesn't go very high, does it?
That's the limitation on that.
What the hell is that thing?
What was that just now?
Whoops!
Ah, come on!
There we go.
In fact, I have a lot of bombs.
Ah, these fucking guys.
Oh, no.
Okay, don't use this item in two tight quarters, otherwise it's terrible.
How we doing?
I think we're okay here.
Gimme.
Let me actually open this.
Put in my money.
So the...
Actually, I don't have that many bombs.
Just bomb the shit out of it.
Oof.
Ah, the projectiles.
Oh, no.
Hey.
I need to find the angle here.
There we go.
Look how much HP they have.
Why?
Why is it so extreme?
Like, what's with the jump here?
In HP?
They went from, like...
Having no HP to being insane bullet sponges.
Like, what?
And I'm dying to small projectiles.
I can't see!
Fucking kill it quick.
Come on.
I can't get that in there.
Ah, this sorta works.
You know what?
Fuck them.
I don't have to fight you.
I'm going my own path.
Whoop!
Okay.
We made it.
We are here.
But something tells me I shouldn't go down just yet.
I need to heal.
Let me quickly put on Obsidian Skin.
Uh-oh.
These guys have no HP at all.
What?
I expected these guys to be insane now.
You saw that?
They instantly died.
Oh!
Fireball out of nowhere.
Off screen.
That's nice.
Gotta go back.
Good thing I just put all my gold in my piggy bank.
Look at this.
In instant clean inventory.
Is that just not the best thing ever?
Look at this.
Already ready to go.
How is that not incredible?
There we go.
I'm gonna speedrun through this section.
Speedrun.
I'm just going to the same path I went before.
Kind of a weird path I took, but whatever.
Like, look at these small projectiles.
You almost can't see them.
And they take like one third of your HP.
And they shoot them so frequently.
It is the most insane enemy ever.
The hardest enemy in the game, probably.
There you go.
One at a time I can handle.
Oh!
Fire Imp.
Wait, why is that here?
Oh, don't even think about it.
Okay, we made it.
Ah!
No, hold on, there's a fucking turtle on us.
Okay, I need to heal.
Go in here and hide.
Okay, nothing will hit me now, right?
We're safe.
I'm just throwing bombs out there, just for good measure.
Gotta get rid of them anyway.
We got a guy up there.
Could I?
Ah, they don't have enough bounce power.
Okay, I'm sort of gaining some HP here.
Obsidian skin now.
There we go.
And let's also go with...
Thorns.
Why not?
Let's go vid...
Nah, not invisibility.
Magic power.
So that should do... how much now?
Uh-oh, it's the protectile people.
Just...
Oh, look at the small protectiles!
Why are they here?
Oh my god!
Oh!
Bro, what is this enemy?
Hello?
Stop following me!
I want peace!
Leave me alone, dammit!
Why are things so easy to kill down here?
I mean, not the bees, of course, or the hornets, or whatever.
Like the other guys down here.
Actually, hold on, I wanna try and fish here.
It's probably gonna be really dumb, but...
I gotta try it.
It actually works?
Or what?
Wait a bit.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Nevermind.
Oh, I need to be careful not accidentally killing one of those guys with the doll attached.
Let's quickly chest again.
We got a guy incoming.
We're fine.
Is this gonna do anything?
I don't think so.
Yeah, I don't think it's doing anything.
Like, these guys are so easy to kill!
I would have thought this place would be even harder, but apparently it's not.
What was this again?
Oh, Hellstone.
I'll take a bit of that, I guess.
Why not?
Got a pot over here.
Whoops, didn't mean to go all the way down there.
Okay, I don't think there's anything...
I mean, I already looted all the chests down here.
Actually, hold on, have I been to the...
I haven't even been to the right end.
Let's go all the way to the right, just to have it explored, you know?
Like, from a completionist point of view here.
Am I hitting anything?
Oh, look, it's also here.
Cobalt, thank you.
I wonder if there's titanium down here.
That's actually what I'm here for.
That was the goal of the expedition.
Give me a loan.
Nice.
Yeah, now we reach the end.
Is there anything down here?
It's just lava, okay.
All right.
Well, we have been all the way to the west and all the way to the east now.
We have confirmed there is nothing there.
Man, these things they're shooting are actually dangerous.
Let me go up here.
Ah, here we go.
Ori, Calcum, and a lot of it.
Beautiful.
There we go.
Where should I go next?
Whoops.
I don't know if I want to go...
Man, I can't even have like two seconds to open the map here before I get attacked again.
Okay, quickly out.
Let's go somewhere else.
That wasn't that cool.
In fact, I want to go back to...
Where was it?
This place right here with the unicorn.
I want to check that out again.
Wait, a bone serpent kite.
Oh, on windy days, I see.
All right, look at that.
Pretty cool, I guess.
A werewolf.
How do you liken the flames?
Honestly, hello?
These things could be nice against the wave event, where they come in waves.
It's a little hard to aim with, though.
Against flying things.
That's fine.
All right, let's put this in the weird box, miscellaneous.
Ash grass seeds.
That's new.
Put it in here.
And look at this inventory, still completely clean.
Squeaky clean.
I'm so happy I went through the ordeal.
And fixed up the whole management last time.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
What is going on here?
Why is this all shit right now?
What the fuck?
This shit is spreading.
That's why there are these goddamn enemies here.
I was wondering why these were here.
Hello?
Will you get out?
Excuse me.
Yeah, you like that?
You like that?
Look at this.
This is actually great for this sort of thing.
And now we can hear that sound again of a big monster on the ground.
Something is lurking down below.
I don't know why I'm killing all these.
Bro, I need to...
fucking cleanse this shit.
Are you kidding me?
Purify.
Dude, I need to talk to Roselva.
I need to see the percentage.
Like, what is going on here?
Okay, hold on.
Nice.
Bro, this weapon is actually better than I initially thought.
This is a good weapon.
It has good DPS.
Okay, so the shit is happening in the world right now.
That is out of my control and I'm scared.
I'm scared.
What's happening?
It makes me uneasy.
What's... oh yeah, right, these things.
That means we're here.
Give me that.
Cool.
Actually, hold on.
Dude, I'm gonna try and fish here.
Can I fish here?
Oh, maybe this is too small, actually.
Let's see.
I think we need a specific size of water here.
Let's try this one.
Oh, wait, yeah, yeah, let's try this one.
Leave me alone when I'm fishing.
I should go invisible.
Invisibility.
There, you can't see me.
Nobody's fishing.
I just briefly appeared.
Man, why can't I fish?
Fishing in lava would have been so cool.
Maybe it's because this is sort of counting as a smaller one.
Wait a minute.
Let's see, come on.
Hey, there we go.
There we fucking go.
Maybe that's the issue in the lava.
Maybe I was fishing from too small of a volume.
Specular fish.
That's new, isn't it?
Chaos fish.
Ooh, am I gonna be able to get the Ebon, Ebon koi?
Princess fish.
Dude, I need to put on my...
It's time for the crate.
Crate potion.
And let's do the other one.
Sonar.
We're going full fishing now.
This is now a fishing stream.
Pearlwood crate.
There we go.
Mithril crate.
What?
Okay, I'm not opening these yet.
We're gonna have an opening, a box opening session after this.
Nice music.
Oh, another crate.
Oh, the crate potion is doing work.
Love it.
I'm so excited now.
What is a princess fish?
Just a material.
Oh, crates everywhere.
Armored cave fish.
Oh, broke.
Mithril crate.
Frickin' awesome.
This music makes me think of a fantasy castle or something like that.
You know?
Maybe you're in the mage quarter of the castle or something?
I mean, I don't even really need the sonar, because I want to grab everything I'm getting out of this here.
Maybe it does reduce the amount of times the thing will break.
Maybe I don't take the base.
I think it's bass, right?
It's not bass.
Bass is something that drops.
You know, this is a great place for a house as well.
Speaking of, I know that the wizard would like to live in a tower.
In the hallow.
So I'm gonna make that happen for him.
In fact, I'll do that today.
That sounds like fun.
I'm gonna try and make the tower from World of Warcraft, like I talked about.
I don't know if you know what I'm talking about at all, but in World of Warcraft, I'm thinking specifically about Elwyn Forest.
There's like a...
Well, there's towers all over the place in that world, but in that place, there's like this tower in the middle of the forest, and it looks really nice.
I don't want bass.
Look how many crates I got.
Specular fish.
I feel like I've seen that in an ingredient for something that I wanted to craft and I didn't have it at the time.
Armored cave fish?
Can I maybe use that to make defense potions?
Mercer has arrived.
I gotta talk to him.
20 seconds of crate.
I need to make more spelunking potions.
So I'm going to go back.
I'm going to talk to the merchant.
I'm going to make spelunker potions.
That's the plan.
So many bays.
Oh, wait, wait.
I need to read it up above.
No.
You know what I mean?
Great.
I need max.
What is this?
I'm hearing glimmering.
Oh, it's this guy.
It's the pixie.
I see.
I kind of want to try and put a pixie in the shimmer.
See what happens then.
Will it become even more glimmering?
Will it shimmer so bright?
More crates.
Is that... hold on.
Is that right there?
Is that the titanium?
Kind of looks like it a little bit.
Thank you.
Man, look how many crates I got.
I got three Mythril crates, 14 Pearlwood crates.
So I guess Mythril is very rare.
Prismite.
Wait a minute.
That's an ingredient for something I was trying to craft.
100%.
I forgot what it was.
But I'll check it when I get back.
Hell yeah, dude.
I just need to fish a lot, actually.
Maybe if I fished for longer in the Crimson area, I would have gotten the Ebon Koi.
Okay, when these two minutes are up for the crate, I'm gonna go back.
That's the plan.
Ah, fuck.
Didn't want that base.
Pearlwood.
Don't click it.
I will take the Specular Fish.
What is that?
Oh, it's the Sonar.
No, it broke on the crate.
That's horrible.
What is this Chaos Fish anyway?
I feel like that's also rare.
Look at the color of it.
Like red.
I actually don't know what the order here is of rarity.
I think this is the rarest, just because I only got one of them.
Like this beige color.
This red one is very rare.
Green is like uncommon, I guess.
That's how I see that.
Nice.
Can we get one more or two more crates in before the timer runs?
Oh, I don't have Sonar anymore.
Come on, one more.
Crate, crate, crate.
Come on, crate.
Five seconds.
One more, come on.
Dang it.
Okay, there we go.
We call.
Let's quickly talk to the traveling merchant.
Where is he?
He's up there on the roof.
My dude.
Come on, have a look.
I will.
You sell the Gattlegator DPS meter.
I'll take it.
Go block ears.
No, thank you.
Code one.
Uh, do I want that?
Isn't that kind of shit?
Then I can't really trust these items.
I need to test them.
Because sometimes they do things that you don't know they do until you do it.
You know what I do?
All right, it's time to open some crates.
Let's go.
Oh, cobalt ore in that.
More bait.
Under potion.
Let me go over here so we can read the text.
Palladium?
The hell is that?
Dude, I love opening crates.
Mithril bar.
And more masturbate.
Fantastic.
All right.
Click the button.
Everything goes in.
Now we got to talk to our local guy, Jeff.
Who for some reason is not hanging out in the place that I designated for him.
In fact, he's all the way over here.
Jeff.
Tell me about this prismite.
That's it.
It was for the potion.
Oh, okay.
That's really it, huh?
Wow, this must be a really good potion then.
Like, not something to use lightly.
I mean, it's nice.
20%, I guess.
Specular.
Oh, recall.
Oh, no, no, nevermind.
I thought it was the other one.
Ooh, love potion.
You know what I think this is for?
You know how some NPCs don't like each other?
Maybe this will force them to like each other.
Like, if you really want these two to live together, you can do it.
With the love potion.
That's what I think.
Chaos fish?
Oh, teleportation!
Firebl- Dude, I'm doing that right now.
I really, really love those potions.
Fireblossom?
Where is it?
We do like that and then one back.
And then we need water.
One back.
And then we go here.
Make it.
Three.
Nice.
Now the DPS meter.
That was used for something.
Then I need to double check as well.
I hate that he's over here.
Jeff!
Oh, hold on, I need to double check where I assigned him.
Tell me.
Metal detector.
Fuck, I don't have- Whoa!
Whoa!
Displace the most valuable ore around you.
Holy shit!
I want that so bad.
Holy fuck.
Metal detector.
Tell me about the palladium.
Is that- It's better than what I have.
Oh, wait a minute.
Uh, nine percent?
No, it's actually worse.
Isn't that ten percent, uh...
Oh, it has different stats, I guess.
Can mine Mithril and Orykalkum?
But so can the one I have right now.
Right?
Can mine...
Edimentite.
What the fuck is Edimentite?
I haven't even seen that.
Okay, well...
Mithril?
Can mine- Okay, let's see.
Sixteen defense.
This is just increased damage.
Increase maximum mana, fifteen percent?
Not bad.
Mithril.
Huh?
Okay.
I'm gonna actually try this real quick.
It's just a- It's just a yo-yo.
What's so amazing about it?
Mirza was departed, that's fine.
All right, as I expected- Whoop!
I took damage from something.
I'm not sure what I took damage from.
I want to keep these in here.
Sort.
Click this button.
And then we go into the ores.
Deposit all the ores.
Fishing.
Former climbing stuff.
Precise shoes.
Wait, is this the same?
Slide down walls.
Improve the combined with climbing claws.
Oh, I think I already did this, didn't I?
I did combine this already.
Let me do it again.
Because why not?
Yeah, I think I made ninja something gear.
It may even be here somewhere.
Put it in there.
So not- This one I want to sell.
This one I want to sell.
And then we can put this one in here.
Turn that into that.
And now inventory's clean.
Inventory clean.
Buy my stuff.
There you go.
Okay, what's next?
I kind of want to go fishing again.
How's my crate potion situation?
Oh, I wanted to make spelunker.
Let's do that.
No, this one.
And I got to talk to Jeff again, because he's the one with the recipes.
Spelunk?
Oh, I already have one bungalow, I think.
This is not worth it.
I can't make it right now.
Unfortunately, it ain't happening.
Fuck it.
Let's go back.
I like Lion Pines.
He's just hanging out up here, chilling.
Where do I want to go?
Where should I go?
I kind of want to go back to this place, actually.
Yeah, let's go back there.
I love this house so much.
Wait a minute.
My fucking work is gone.
I purified this.
Hello?
Why is this not purified?
Get away from me.
Also, apparently, there's someone I can purify down below in the caverns.
Fucking...
This whole place is completely fucked.
All right, that worked pretty well.
Let's just do it all the way.
Maybe that's how that works, actually.
You just got to...
You can't leave one spot, you know what I mean?
Oh my god, that thing has so much HP for some reason.
Okay, that works.
What's up, guys?
Check that out.
Beautiful stuff.
Actually, it's not...
Why is this not the normal water?
Dammit.
Yeah, look, it's fucking spreading!
Just everywhere, everywhere.
I think I need to...
The surface here.
Like, all of it.
Oh, what happened?
What?
Oh, wait, what?
Why can't I attack?
Oh, I'm silent.
I'm silenced.
I thought it was out of mana, and I couldn't understand it because I had plenty of mana.
Oh, I don't have any more powder.
Ah, whatever.
I guess we'll do this later.
It wasn't always spreading.
Probably happened when I unleashed whatever the fuck it was I unleashed.
The unleashing...
Actually, this place is not being...
Hold on, let me pay attention here.
Let's try something.
Right here at the entrance to the cave.
That's where the limit is there.
Let's see if that changes next time we come back.
Need to test this.
Oh my god.
Oh, that was kind of sick.
I nailed that just now.
That was sick.
That was skills.
This weapon is super awkward in some circumstances.
It's super good in some circumstances.
But in others, it's just straight up terrible.
Yeah, the thing about this one as well is if you hit it while they're in water, it doesn't do anything.
Because it's fire that you're throwing.
Actually, I want to fish a bit more here.
That was so relaxing before.
Need to do more of that.
Same spot, dude.
We're chilling here.
And let me also put on my...
Invise a bit, sir.
Can't see me.
Get away.
Ah, crate potion, of course.
That's the last we have.
Let's just use that.
When no more crate, we are done with the hate.
I don't even know what I wanted to say.
We are done with the fishing expedition.
Whoops.
Take the wrong button.
Thank you.
I want more mythical crates.
That's what I want.
Yeah!
Oh, did I check the armored cave fish?
I don't think I checked that with Jeff.
We got to check that one.
Hopefully, it can make armor defense for us.
I'm thinking of the armored cart from Zelda.
That's a trap right there.
I spot that.
Balloon puffer fish.
Ha!
Like a balloon, but it's an arcane megaphone immune to silence.
Yo, that would have been great just before, wouldn't it?
When I was silenced.
The dark shard.
I need to test that with Jeff also, because I kind of forgot what that was.
What else did I get?
I think I'm getting a lot of random new stuff here.
That's about it, I think.
You know the best thing about those crates is, they contain potions.
Random potions.
Useful potions.
And it's such a pain to craft potions, so it's a very welcome thing to get a potion.
Nice.
I actually have more Mythril than Pearl would crates right now.
I wonder how well the invisibility...
Let's say I stand still in an area with enemies.
Will they even notice me?
All right, let's try that.
My glasses are so dirty, I need to clean them once.
But my microfiber cloth.
There we go.
I was like, wait, is that the ore I'm looking at?
No, it's just a fucking speck of dirt on my glasses.
I hear the shimmer again, or the glimmer.
Oh, it's up there.
Come on, one more crate before the buff runs out.
One more.
Uno mas por favor.
No, not the pass.
Come on.
One more.
Yeah!
Got one last crate there.
Amazing.
All right.
I love the music in this place.
Let me get rid of that trap right there.
Oh!
Wait, where'd he go?
Oh, I got it.
Nice.
Give me lead.
Oh, we've got more of these things.
Destroy them.
Titanium!
Cobalt!
Nice!
Give me more of everything.
Oh, look, I've been here.
Can you tell?
Because there's a corpse.
Or a...
What do you call it?
Actually, do I want to go a place I've already been?
Come on, get out of the wall.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go back up.
Whoops.
I'm gonna go to the left over here.
I've been here as well.
Oops.
I haven't been to this little area down here.
Give me all these.
I should be on the moon...
Look out for moon glow.
What is that down there?
What is that?
Looks like an enemy.
Oh my god.
Whoop!
Thank you.
There's a little trap down there.
I spotted it.
Let's take care of that first.
I can't see shit.
Please!
There we go.
Trap gone.
What's this?
Ruby.
Oh.
Looked like some kind of...
I don't even know what that is.
Keep digging.
Did it.
Why's there this huge deposit of water in there?
Let's drain it.
Well, somewhat.
There.
You're free!
You little bastard.
Okay, I really need to be on the lookout for titanium here.
Wait, I saw you.
I saw you.
Fuck you.
I've seen your tricks.
Do we have any titanium?
I'm really scanning here.
I don't see anything sparkly.
Get rid of this guy.
Thank you.
Whoops.
Let's just drain.
Hey, look at that!
There's a guy in here.
The thing keeps going out because of the water.
I want to drain this entire place.
Non-shell recover.
Ooh!
Look at this!
Yo, what's this?
Oh, I'm dying, I'm dying.
Yeah.
I can't see shit.
Just go, just go.
Drain the shit out of this place.
We gotta heal.
What is this?
A crystal start!
I needed that.
I don't remember for what, but something.
I remember needing that.
Gimme.
Gimme that.
Oh my god, yes.
Amazing.
So pretty as well.
Oh, look at that.
Let me take this as well.
Lots of amethyst.
Oh man, I can't wait to remind myself what I needed that for, but it was something big.
I remember that much.
Uh-oh.
Burning hell.
All of this is going in my white bag right now, I think.
Where's the only titanium at all?
The dainome.
Pretty cool.
I like it.
You.
Ooh, a chest!
Heavy breathing reed.
Shark bait, gravitation.
I don't really want any of this.
Glow sticks.
You know what, we could actually probably do with doing this.
I'll fill this up.
In fact, let me just quickly open this.
Thingies.
Enchanted sundial.
Allows time to fast forward to dawn one day per week.
No way!
That's freaking awesome!
I like that a lot.
Thank you.
I gotta do more fishing, dude!
The fishing is insane!
It's absolutely wild!
Who are you?
Skeleton archer.
And what's that?
Chaos elemental.
All these new enemies.
There we go.
Did you drop something for me?
Give me more of that.
I'm taking all of these.
It's probably one of these things that I only need to one-off and I'm like collecting a million.
Look at the blur effect on these.
Chaos elemental.
Soul of light!
Yo!
Really?
From these?
Oh boy.
I will be spending time down here, I think.
I think I will be spending some time here.
Just having a talk with the local residents.
Someone's shooting arrows.
Oh!
Spawn right behind me.
But he didn't drop one.
I think it's a very rare drop.
Oh, look at the background!
Look!
Whoops!
I'm taking damage from something, I don't know what is.
Yeah, my fire thing is useless here because of all the water.
Man, my finger hurts from clicking all this.
Look how much HP they have.
I really need a crazy weapon here.
I'm like pressing with my middle finger because my...
Oh, I just got three souls of light.
Dude, for that amount of soul of light, I will keep pressing my finger.
I feel like I'm getting all kinds of things I've been craving for so long down here.
This is the area, man.
This is it.
This is the biome I have been wanting and looking for for so long.
What was that?
Oh, there's a guy here.
Ah!
I can't see shit!
Get away!
Okay,
we're fine.
Drain that shit!
I can't hold it in on unfortunate looks.
Only if they're in line of sight.
My finger hurts.
I'm dying here.
I wonder if this is where Ori Kalkum is from because it's like all purpley and pink.
It's like this place.
Apple pie?
Don't mind if I do.
Dude, oh man, I could have some apple pie right now.
Oh yeah, baby.
Maybe we should get that today.
This guy is mega confused.
He's giga confused.
Sup, mother slime?
The star is falling from the sky.
I'm not sure how much damage they actually do.
Dude, I'm loving this biome.
This biome slaps.
It's difficult, but it has some rewards that I'm very much a fan of.
What's that?
Anglerfish.
Oh, not you.
Please die.
Okay, what am I seeing?
Am I seeing anything special on the horizon here?
Not really.
Let's just go further down.
This whole place, by the way, does not look like a special biome when you look at the map.
Oh wait, it actually does.
Never mind.
I'm wrong.
It does look special.
I guess I just keep collecting this.
Crystal shard.
Wait a minute, look to the left there.
That looks like a weird blend between desert and hallowed.
What's that?
Dreamer ghoul.
Bro, this guy is not dying.
Soul of...
Dude, I'm getting shit tons of Soul of Light.
I have seven!
I think I needed 15 for something big.
Forgot what it was, but it was something very nice.
And I also needed Soul of something else.
Soul of... I don't know, dark or something.
It was Soul of Light and Soul of Dark.
What's that?
Sand poacher.
Oh yeah?
Oh, I just got a mining poacher.
That's big.
I love this weapon.
Let's deposit some money.
Wait,
I think I'm about to die here.
It's very close a lot of the time.
Thank you.
What's that on the ceiling?
Hardened pearl sand block.
Look at these fucking creatures in there.
There's a lot of creatures down there.
Let me throw a bunch of these down there, huh?
Have fun.
Oh, I think things are dying.
Yep.
Oh, they're not too bad, actually.
I thought these guys would be worse.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, I'm in a bad position here.
Thank God they're all confused.
Whoa!
I'm stuck in a corner.
Damn.
Oh, and they keep coming.
I need to...
Actually, I have plenty of mana, never mind.
There you go.
Angle it off that little point there.
Nice.
Thank you.
Dude, I should be using a potion of luck, I think.
I don't even know if I have that.
But there are potions of luck, and maybe it was an item of luck as well, but there was definitely something that increases luck, and it's gotta be just drops, right?
What else could it be?
Maybe that even helps with fishing.
Dude.
A keg?
Where did that go?
Going here?
Used for brewing ale.
Cool.
Uh...
Well...
Pause it all.
Give me these.
Let me eat one of the thorns.
Put that there.
Dream rule.
Nice.
Look at that!
They all drop Soul of Light!
You know, I think it's related to just the biome.
I don't think it's the enemies.
What did I get just now?
Oh, antlion something.
Oof!
Ooh, what's that?
Lamia.
Oh no!
I'm confused!
I'm gonna die here, I think.
I'm confused.
I'm moving the opposite direction where I'm clicking.
This is so unintuitive.
Oh, the other way!
I'm dead.
I don't know where I just died from.
Some little projectile I couldn't see, I guess.
Fuck.
But that was a good run.
That was nice.
You made it a lot...
We made it very far down.
Okay, let's try this here.
Enchanted Sundial.
Hey!
Looks like Abigail and Mackenzie are throwing a party.
Why are we having a party?
Abigail...
Wait.
Koki-ki.
I- wait, Isis?
Don't tell anyone I gave you this, it's a party surprise.
Give me one.
Should you give me something?
Oh, the cake!
Oh!
Put it on the table.
Cake for everyone.
Shit.
Yeah.
Wait, Gelatin Crystal.
Summons Queenslime?
No way!
Light shard.
Wait!
I had a dark shard, didn't I?
Hold on now.
Sort things first.
Inactive stone block.
Let's put that in blocks.
That goes in here as well.
If you want to make an apple pie from scratch, you first have to invent the universe.
I'm going to ask you now, how many successive cuts do I make into an apple pie before we reach down to the smallest building blocks of the universe?
That's what I want to know from you guys.
Crystal shard.
Why is there only one?
Oh wait, did the rest go in here?
So- okay, this one is clean.
This is the mess.
Ludol.
Eighty-two crystal shards.
Let's place the cake here.
We can bruise a male.
How does that work?
Let's see here.
Sell that.
Delete that.
Ancient cloth.
Okay.
Jeff, we have lots to discuss.
Jeff, my man.
Tell me about this one first.
Sharkron balloon.
I can make that.
In fact, let's make that right now.
That's also a material.
Maybe that will leave something completely different down the road.
Awesome.
Look at that.
Menacing sharkron balloon.
I can make that into a pink horseshoe balloon.
Jump height negates fall damage.
Double jump.
Pretty much the same thing I have now.
But it looks different.
I think I even have another magnet.
Why not just do it?
Clean up the inventory a little bit here.
Is that it?
Oh wait, I have this one, I think.
It's the one.
Let's see what happens now.
Wait.
Where's the...
Wait a minute.
Why is this not working?
Was it not a magnet?
Am I remembering wrong here?
Oh a horseshoe.
Fuck.
A horseshoe.
It looked like a magnet because of the shape of it, you know.
Fuck.
Do I have that?
Let's see.
I don't think I do.
Damage per second.
What do I have actually?
Let's just take a quick look.
Honestly, I want to sell these.
I also want to sell these.
And that one.
All these duplicates.
Sell this one as well.
The ice mirror.
I want to check that with Jeff as well.
Hey yo, Jeff.
Man, Jefferson.
Never been to a party before.
You might want to check around with the others.
People sometimes bring out special party favors.
Is that so?
Maybe I will check it with everyone then.
Why do I keep having this?
Tell me about the ice mirror.
All right.
That's the one you use to make a cell phone.
But to make a PDA, I have to use something else, I think.
Hold on, what does this do again?
Makes it GPS.
I need a compass for that though.
I don't know how to get a compass.
Uh,
let's sell these as well.
Light shard.
Skype.
Hold on now.
Wait, soul of light?
Soul of night.
The essence of light creatures.
And then we have the essence of dark creatures.
Ah ha.
Oh.
This is made from a magic missile.
Cute.
Uh, there's so many things I want to do.
Let's quickly clean the inventory here.
What party favors are you talking about?
You have party favors?
Cell, cell, cell, cell, cell.
Cell.
That's good.
I think I also want to sell this.
No, no, leave that for now.
The megaphone, right.
That's the one I wanted to test as well.
Um, what did I just...
What did I want to do just now?
Right, I want to get the soul of light.
I think I put that somewhere.
Where is it?
Soul of light.
Wait, wait, wait.
Didn't I...
I didn't put that anywhere, did I?
Where would I put that?
Materials?
There's no way.
Oh, maybe I did.
Oh, yeah, I already had one soul of light.
So when I auto stacked it, put it in here.
True.
So I have 13 of these.
Take all except one.
And then...
Once again.
What can I...
Okay, yeah, let's actually check this out.
I need just a little bit more soul of light.
And I guess one more light short.
A cool whip.
Soul of night, soul of light.
And frost core.
Wait, light disk?
Huh.
I want to test all of this, dude.
Hello, bar!
How do I make that?
Wait, soul of might.
The essence of the destroyer.
That's got to be from a boss.
A boss called the destroyer.
Soul of light in a bottle.
Rainbow rod.
Soul of sight.
Okay, that's all these different souls.
Meteor staff.
Crystal storm.
Wait, I can actually almost make this.
I can almost make this.
I need just two more soul of light.
Then I can actually make this.
Mechanical eye.
Mechanical skull.
Okay.
Wait, key of light?
Charged with the essence of many souls.
I feel like that's got to work on one of the chests we found in the dungeon to the west.
But it's a bit risky, right?
Because maybe it's not and then it's like wasted a lot of essence of light.
Or soul of light, sorry.
Anyway, for now...
Oh, let's check with the arcane megaphone and ancient cloth.
I want to see what that does.
A megaphone and...
Counter curse mantra.
I can make this.
Nassar, I have that.
Nassar...
Where is it?
There it is.
Look at that stuff.
A counter curse mantra.
Cool.
That's also a material.
Let's check with Jeff on that one.
Holy shit.
Oh, so that's how you make the Ankh Charm.
You need all kinds of...
Oh, so I have that already.
That's nice.
I don't have the plan.
Immunity to weakness and broken armor.
Bro, all of this sounds incredible.
What about the ancient cloth?
Is that incredible?
I can make vanity stuff.
That's not incredible.
Tell me about the light shard again.
I kind of want to make this.
Sky...
By the way, this is a melee weapon.
I don't really want that actually.
No, no, no.
I changed my mind.
I don't want that.
I want some of the magic stuff I can make with Soul of Light.
That's what I want.
And this one is once again used for making celestial cuffs.
Restores mana when damaged.
Hello.
Wait, I can actually...
I think...
Can I make this?
The slimes are gone.
What just happened?
Hello?
Did the slimes just kill my slimes?
Bastards?
How dare they?
No, actually, I don't think I have that item.
Stack, vanity.
Let's put some stuff in.
Ah, no, that's a material.
That's a weird item.
Goes in miscellaneous.
Crystal shard is definitely material here.
Let's put it here, I guess.
Rate of mana.
Oh yeah, put that here.
I have two unicorn heads.
Oh yeah, I haven't checked this either.
Let me check the dark shard in these ones again.
Yeah, let's just do that.
I guess we're doing this anyway.
Jefferson.
Pixie dust, remind me.
Controllable rainbow.
Fairy wings.
99.
Is that related?
Is that...
Is this a joke?
Is this like related to the...
996 Luftbalungs or like Luft...
You know what I mean.
99 air balloons.
Allows flight and slow fall.
Allows flight.
I feel like when they say flight in this game, it's not really flight, is it?
It's falling with style.
Now this one.
That's what I need, dude!
Greater healing potion, I can finally make it!
That's what the crystal shard was for.
Fuck yeah.
Pixie dust though.
Don't have a lot of it.
But I have enough bottled water.
Let's make it, dude.
Let's fucking make it.
Hell yeah.
Now, my mind just blanked.
What the fuck?
What materials were in that?
There was water.
Water.
Vassa.
And then we need the...
pixie dust and the crystal shard, which I have.
I believe I have it here.
Yep.
Oh, leave one of them.
There we go.
And then...
I guess at the potion table here.
Yes!
Wait, it makes three at a time?
Oh, okay, never mind.
Yeah, okay, I see.
Make all of it.
And I'm saving this for bosses, by the way.
This is normal.
This is fine for exploring with this right here.
That is what I need when I fight a boss.
All right.
Put the stuff in there.
And that.
And that, and that, and this.
So I wanted to check the magic conch as well.
La, la, la, la, la.
Apple pie, I will definitely save that for a rainy day.
That's a good buff.
In fact, let's put it in here.
There we go.
Very nice.
It's conch time!
Shell phone!
Right click to toggle destination.
Oh my god!
Wait a minute.
Allows you to return home at will?
To toggle destination?
Demon conch.
If you listen closely, you can hear screams.
That's, that's funny.
I like that.
Pretty nice.
But for now, let's put it back in here.
Very cool.
The dirt?
I don't want that.
Put it in here.
What, what, what used to be in this last spot?
Huh?
What did I have there?
Shit, I don't remember.
Okay.
Nice, nice, nice.
Um, what was I doing?
I died somewhere.
I died here.
Yeah, look how that looks.
Very cool.
In fact, I'm going to go over here and dig straight down into it.
No, I'm going to go into this cave and then down.
Oh, but no, that's the really difficult cave, isn't it?
I don't know if I want to do that.
Also, didn't a merchant arrive?
Merchantus?
Where are you?
Septimus the Elder's Lime and Isaac is hanging out over there.
Maybe we should pay them a visit again.
But not right now.
Septimus the Great.
Man, this fucking area is all fucked up again.
Look.
Bro, this pixie dust bullshit ain't working.
I've been scammed.
It's snake oil.
What the hell kind of bullshit is Rossella selling me?
Speaking of Rossella.
You know what?
Let's go have a word with her, huh?
Because I feel like she sold me a raw deal.
And I need to exchange a few things with her about that.
Wait a minute.
I'm an idiot.
I should teleport.
Okay,
nice.
Get out of my sight.
Bro, this weapon right here is actually changing everything for me right now.
This arrived since I was here last time.
I think because I clicked on one of the altars, it sort of put that there, among other places.
Because I would have seen that on the way up last time.
Okay, how are we doing?
Ah, the sands of time are flowing.
And well, you're not aging very gracefully.
All right, status.
The robust can is 10% hallow and 17% crimson.
We have a lot of work to do.
Okay, you want me to go everywhere and throw this shit around?
I tried that already.
What else you got?
Wait, hallowed seeds.
Hold on now.
What do you mean?
Also, wait a minute.
Pumpkin seeds.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
Potted hallowed tree?
Is that the one?
Where's the hallowed planter box?
Maybe it doesn't matter.
Let me try one of these.
Let's try and put that there.
Oh wait, I need a bit more of that.
Like that.
Can be placed.
No, it can't.
All right, fine.
Solitude.
Yeah, whatever.
It never said hallow before, by the way.
This is new.
Seven.
What happens if I don't work?
Rosalva.
By the way, look at that dolphin over there doing trick jumps.
Ten percent hallow.
And is this like the forces of good and evil?
The hallow is the good stuff.
Crimson is bad.
Depending on which side you're on, of course.
Well, Rosalva, I've been trying to throw those goddamn powders.
Cleanse is the, yeah, cleanse is the evil.
It's not a material either, so I can't really...
Wait, do I just buy a shit ton of this?
And that can't be how I'm supposed to do this.
Really?
That's what you want me to do?
You have a lot of work.
You want me to just...
Fine.
What needs cleansing?
We have an area here.
I shall cleanse the world for you, ma'am.
I shall cleanse it all.
Or you needed cleansing, you came to the right person.
Because I am the cleanser.
I'm going to try and cleanse.
So what I think is happening here is that I tried cleansing the desert and it failed because I think I didn't cleanse all of this area.
So if I cleanse...
Actually, this is kind of a small area too.
If I cleanse just this part, maybe it will not go back.
Let's try and remember.
17% she said.
I actually want to see if that updates in real time.
I guess it does, right?
Up that booroo.
Wow!
That's some bullshit.
Fucking tortoise is harder than any enemy in this game.
I want to teleport.
Teleportation.
Yeah, I can't teleport there because it's fucked.
All right, I guess we can do it in this area.
This is a bit tedious.
There's no way this is how I'm supposed to do this.
I guess it doesn't take that long, I guess.
But look at this.
What about below?
Look, it's fucking going back immediately.
Huh?
All right, fuck it, let's just hurry.
Let's do this entire region quickly.
Maybe that's the trick.
It's like a good cleansing here.
It doesn't help that there's monsters everywhere that stops me from doing the thing.
Dark... wait, dark shard!
From here.
Oh, it actually makes sense.
Good and evil.
Soul of Light comes from Hallo, and then we have Crimson Evil.
They probably drop Soul of Night as well.
That's what I think.
Look at that tree, it just became green.
It's kind of satisfying.
Did he just use the the good mana potion or healing potion?
I don't think he did, hopefully not.
Slime is falling from the sky now.
Great.
Also, look how much of this powder I'm using.
Like, can I just please just purify in peace here?
Get away from me.
What happens if I throw this inside the Hallo?
Nothing happens.
Okay, let's go check with Rosalva.
It looks good.
Oh yeah, look!
I think maybe it worked.
Ah, we've got more here.
Let me just let me just cleanse everything I see on the way there, actually.
Also, look at this area.
This is also...
Wait, wait a minute.
Wait, what?
There's a difference between these two biomes.
Oh my god.
Burn in hell!
So do I...
Do you also have to...
Oh my god.
I'm dying.
Oh, there's a spot there.
Missed a spot.
Fixed.
But look at that.
It's like...
I don't understand this system.
It's mega weird.
Actually, I still have a lot of purification powder.
Purify the earth.
I'm going to predict she's going to say percentage nine percent.
If it actually changes.
All this is clean.
That's nice.
Getting rid of...
Oh, see daisy.
Whoa.
Ah!
Why am I slow?
I'm dying.
Nine seconds until heal.
Oh, come on.
Go!
Oh, what's that?
But,
yeah, we healed.
Perfect.
Look at that.
The skill's on display here.
Oh, look at that.
Actually, you can do some pretty crazy tricks here.
If you time it.
Hold on, let me try.
Ah, wait, that was bad.
Yeah, we gained some...
It's a little bit finicky, but we can definitely do it.
All right, Rosalva.
I've been doing what you told me to do.
Be safe.
Terraria needs you.
How about you?
You're just standing here doing nothing.
Literally nothing changed.
But maybe it's just a thing that needs a bit of time to update.
I don't know.
Hey, get out of here.
Get... close the door.
Notice this.
This entire tunnel used to be crimson.
But look at this.
This is different up here.
Huh?
Wait, what is this then?
I don't understand.
Oh my god, look at all the slimes.
They're trying to get to me.
Do you want to fight?
Yo, Rosalva's doing the kind of spell.
Oh, wait, you should just explode them on the roof.
Once again, magic missile.
It's incredible.
Oh, wait a minute, speed up slimes.
Queen slime, huh?
I kind of want to try that.
Speed decay.
Sully, what's up?
Why can't your slime just be like Sully here?
Something to aspire to.
Change the... there we go.
You know, one way to do this is actually just sit here and wait for all the slimes to gather up on the roof and then just kill them.
Because they're gonna jump up there like...
like dumb slimes.
What are you gonna do?
Wait, you open the door.
The slimes are sentient.
King slime.
Okay, I was kind of expecting maybe the queen slime here, but...
Uh-oh.
Let me try my specialized weapon here.
Oh my god, look how good it is.
Oh, this guy has nothing on me.
Which I like.
But he doesn't really drop anything, does he?
Look at all the slimes.
Oh, they spot right on top of me.
Come on.
Dude, look at all the slimes.
This is a fucking slaughter.
Jesus.
Oh my god.
This is a legit way to get some money.
They're cleansed.
Is Rosalba dead?
Oh my god, everyone died here.
I'm so sorry.
What did I get?
Treasure bag.
Ninja...
wait.
Hasty royal solidifier.
Squirts a harmless stream of slime.
Pfft.
Why?
Hey, you like slime?
Oh no, I oiled the seagull.
I shall oil the ocean.
Oh, that's terrible.
Don't do that, kids.
Don't oil the ocean.
What else did I get?
Ninja hood.
Celestial slime staff.
What is that?
Summon.
A little slime.
A baby slime.
That's so cute.
I like it.
Pirate map!
Summon's a pirate invasion.
Do I want that?
Sounds like I don't want that.
Why?
I mean, maybe I want that.
Maybe I do want that.
Can I do this?
This would be the place to do it, right?
At the beach?
Pirate invasion?
I think that's a good idea.
Okay.
Anyway, let's head back.
Actually, whoa, whoa.
Was there anything else I wanted to do here?
Before I go back?
I like this song right here.
That's a nice song.
Wait, who's that?
Koki the Witch Doctor.
All right, let's head back.
Actually, kind of nice that I appear right at my storehouse too.
I sort of planned that, but not like all the way, you know?
It was a happy accident.
Let me talk to Koki.
Abigail may heal your body, but I can make you embody healing.
That's such a good sentence.
Yeah, okay.
Imbuing station.
I feel like I'm missing something big with this one.
Maybe this is the whole trick to getting better weapons.
Weapon embumement flasks.
You know, blow gun.
Mackenzie.
Are you selling anything?
Oh yeah, you sell the jousting stuff.
Yeah, okay.
Critter shampoo.
I actually just want to check with everyone.
Fjell, the goblin tinker has arrived.
Oh, he died probably over here, didn't he?
Yeah, that's probably what happened.
He died.
Oh, you're back now, but you're here.
Silia.
I wish Maurice would stop floating with me.
Doesn't he realize I'm 500 years old?
Well, that just means you have a lot of experience.
Hano.
You still sell nothing but bullshit.
Maurice?
Same shit?
Yeah.
What about Herael?
I'm intrigued by the ice rod.
I'm buying it.
Let's try that.
Oh, wait.
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
Is this like that cloud that rained blood?
But like now it's ice.
Maybe it's just a way to block access.
You know, you do that and things can't cross.
Yeah, I think that's what it is.
Yeah.
Like if you're in a boss fight or whatever and you want to block his attacks, you put that up.
I don't know.
Something like that.
Let's put some miscellaneous stuff in.
Solidifier.
I kind of want to sell.
Actually, we can put one here.
Put it...
I don't even know, man.
On top of the roof.
Put it there.
That's fine.
Oh, yeah.
The masterful magic missile was an ingredient for something I wanted to make.
But it's an ingredient for something else.
It doesn't seem like...
Okay, yeah.
This is a melee weapon.
And I don't actually want to make this anyway.
I regret my decision again.
Pirate map.
That is a weird item.
It goes in miscellaneous.
Hello, seeds.
Let's put that in here.
Ash grass seeds.
Someone's a baby slime.
Nines.
That's terrible.
That's like terrible.
I'm going to put that in weapons.
Countess magic.
Okay.
And then...
Wait a minute.
This is better.
Oh, yeah.
It's because I have better items now.
Like, look.
Eighteen summon damage.
Nine summon damage.
This is way better.
This is like an insane one that I got very early.
It uses seven mana.
This one uses seven mana too.
At the aqua scepter.
Huh.
Wait a minute.
How much damage does this actually do?
I got a DPS thingy.
I can check that.
Here.
Look.
DPS meter.
I want to put this in over here actually.
Let me check this.
Like 200 damage per second.
That's 180.
About...
That's higher.
Just a little bit.
Harder to aim though.
The mythical flower of fire though.
Here we go.
I predict 400.
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
Almost 500.
That's pretty dope.
This one is pretty good.
It's pretty good.
The magic missile.
It's also pretty good, but how good is it really?
Okay, it's actually the worst.
But the good thing about this is it's seeking, right?
It seeks the enemies around corners, which is a big deal.
So a lot of DPS is lost with the other weapons when you miss.
With this one, you don't miss very much, right?
So that's a hard thing to quantify, I guess.
The ice rod.
It actually does decent damage.
Yo, the DPS meter is kind of amazing.
Pretty cool.
In fact, I'm going to test some weapons now, since I have that.
Let's test...
Not melee weapons.
Let's go with...
You know what?
Let's try a bow.
Oh, wait, we need shadow flame arrows.
I have no idea how to make that.
Let's try this one.
I'm actually curious how much DPS that is.
What do we have up here?
Human scythe.
This one is going to have pretty good DPS, I think.
Let me check all these.
Oops, come on.
Like 120, 150.
But then sometimes this thing jumps and does something incredible.
Like 100 on average here.
It's not very good.
It used to be very good.
Not anymore.
It's very variable.
This one, I predict 320.
Oh, it's actually way lower than I thought.
Wow.
Okay, what about the flame lash?
Wow!
Okay, maybe I got some lucky crits there in the beginning.
It's about 200.
All right.
Cool.
Okay, so the best one I have is by far the mythical flower of fire, which is no surprise, because that's also what it felt like.
It felt way better, like when you actually hit things.
Now, let's try a couple...
No, because I don't have the gear for that, so it's not a fair comparison, I guess.
All right, put some stuff in here.
Nice rod.
I want to keep this, I think.
This is my new magic missile.
It does the same thing as magic missile, but a little bit better, it seems?
Mushroom?
Do I really not have any of those in my...
No way.
I did, okay.
All right.
Actually, there's something I want to try.
Speaking of range it here.
This one I want to try.
And I think the shotgun is going to be insane.
It's just a test, but the thing is you never hit with most of these.
Especially not at range, but I think the shotgun is going to be 250.
All right, it's not bad, but that's when you hit everything, with everything, right?
It's actually not that great, now that I look at it.
But wait, wasn't there actually something I could do with this?
How is this better?
It's slower.
It's got to have something that is not written here, because this makes no sense to me stat-wise.
I don't have Soul of Night, fuck.
I guess I could...
Is this also a material?
No, it's not, okay.
Well, all right.
Soul of Night.
I think I know where to get that.
Okay, that's not bad either.
Actually, wait a minute.
I think I know how to maybe get those arrows.
I guess I want that one.
Put these back.
Put this one back there.
This one there.
I'm going to just try and ask Jeff about it.
Wait, where's my arrows?
Oh, wait, did I sell all the arrows?
Maybe I did, actually.
I have some here.
Oh, but these are not...
Never mind.
Fuck, I don't have it.
All right.
I'm going to try that next time.
I guess I could just ask and be like, Hey, sup, dude.
How do I make this?
Um, all right.
Well, that was kind of eye opening to get an idea of the DPS.
These things do.
You know, like one thing is feeling it.
The other thing is seeing the numbers.
So that's kind of a big deal.
What is this again?
The imbuing station.
Used to craft the weapon.
Yeah, but how?
Oh, Aiden has arrived.
Aiden!
What do you sell?
A crown.
So that's the wand.
Summons SD.
Sure.
Oh, wait, it's a platinum.
Oh, wait, I can actually sell it back.
Well, maybe I want it.
Jallis, he's still the catalligator.
Fess.
Life form analyzer.
Okay.
All right, then.
Get rid of that.
That's just evidence for something that never happened.
Give me this as well.
I will be carrying this around with me.
Let's sort this and put it there.
This is all like the utilities for fights, you know?
Man, what the fuck did I used to have on here?
Was it really the bug net?
I don't remember.
All right, well, that's good.
I feel like this is a good way to stop here with a clean inventory and a clean slate, so to speak.
For next time, so I don't have to spend a million years sorting the inventory next time I start.
So yeah, that's it for today.
I wasn't actually planning on streaming Sunday, but I really felt like it.
And I had a bit of time.
So I was like, fuck it, let's do it.
Let's stream a bit.
Play some Terraria.
I'll be here for like a couple minutes and then I'm going to go out and touch grass.
Weather is actually amazing.
And maybe I'll get that.
Uh, apple pie that I talked about.
How's everybody doing, huh?
Good stream, great progress.
Yeah, even if there's not great progress, it's still progress, right?
I'm getting somewhere, slowly but surely.
Thanks for the stream.
Have a good one.
You too, Jorik.
Thanks for stopping by.
Thanks for checking it out.
Hold on a second, actually.
Employee427.
I love that name.
Welcome to the potato.
Good to have you.
What is your profile picture?
Looks like a bird.
I'm trying to lean in.
I can't quite tell.
Like with a big beak or something?
I'm not sure what that is.
Undamaged.
Member for one month.
The can.
For being here.
I just merged two sentences together.
Thanks for being here.
Yeah, the demon emote.
Crowwater made those.
They're pretty cool.
Hello, Chillkruhte.
We get the jakop.
We get the gudhte.
What do I need, Chillkruhte?
Well, I'm an espier.
Is it good weather there?
We chillik bistu.
I am pretty chill, I would say.
Whoo-hoo!
Johnny, why is this ending?
What's up, Haggler?
Too bad, huh?
Or maybe too good.
I don't know.
I know that some people like to watch these things at like 150% speed or something.
I like to do the same thing with a lot of stuff.
Ain't nobody got time for real time.
Flies99998.
What's up, dude?
Hey, Oliver.
First time catching most of a stream live.
This was a fun one.
Thank you.
I had a great time.
Quasi-manipulation.
Good to see you again.
So, no Monday stream then?
Monday's...
No, probably not.
No.
Also, because tomorrow is the Clem Weekly in StarCraft 2.
And I have to watch that, of course.
Chat was happy when you finally switched to the flame instead of the magic missile.
Nice.
Space lover.
Hey, man.
I've seen you forever.
Good to see you again.
Have you heard about the Stanley Parable?
I have indeed heard about the Stanley Parable.
And it's actually on the list of games that I need to play.
That list is on Discord in the game section.
It's pinned up there.
Or maybe it's a thread.
I'm not sure.
It's either one of those.
And you can check out what's on that list.
I'm intending to play it one day.
Yeah.
Chat is kind of wild with subtle spoilers.
Dude, I'm an expert at dodging spoilers.
It's so easy to spot.
When I scan through the comments, within the last...
Within the first two words, I know whether or not this person is trying to spoil something.
Or not.
I'm not in a malicious way or anything.
It can be both, right?
But I automatically just skip over that and read the next.
It's like almost automatic at this point.
Of course, the mods help a lot.
Removing some of it.
But yeah, I'm like an expert at that, at this point.
But yes, please don't spoil anything.
Of course, not on purpose.
But also, sometimes you do it not on purpose.
Just keep it in mind.
Not to say anything about the game.
I would like to discover that for myself.
What game is up next for streaming after Terraria?
Something more chill, I think.
I think I'm gonna go Noida.
That was the one I wanted to play, actually, instead of Terraria.
But then I changed my mind at the last minute.
Yeah.
After beating Inscription?
I think after Inscription...
And don't quote me on this, but...
I think I'm gonna play Subnautica Below Zero, finally.
Guys, I was kidding with the chill.
I know it's a hard game, people told me.
But it's a roguelite, right?
And it's supposed to be hard like that.
That's the whole design of it.
You get stronger every run, stuff like that, right?
Actually, don't tell me.
Don't tell me.
Guys, Noida is so chill.
Lightning buff.
Isn't Noida the opposite?
Never played it.
I have a general idea of how the game works.
I saw Man vs Gameplay it for like 10 minutes, many years ago.
I think at least it was Man vs Game.
The thing that looked very cool is the simulation of all the pixels.
That shit gets me going, you know?
I love it.
It's Tears of the Kingdom on the list.
I'm not sure, actually.
But it's probably a game I'll play at some point.
Not anytime soon, though.
Have you heard about the Rainworld Watcher DLC?
Yes, I have.
Sounds interesting.
Well, I didn't really read too much about it.
I just saw that it was there.
I was like, cool.
That's awesome that they're still supporting the game and updating it.
Half slash, will you ever stream a game not blind?
Yeah, well, I stream Starcraft quite regularly on my Twitch channel.
And I've played that game since 2012.
So that's definitely not blind.
But I mean, I like to experience new games all the time.
I don't really like to replay games very much.
There are a few exceptions, such as Kerbal Space Program and similar games to that, you know, that have a lot of replay value.
And World of Warcraft stuff like that could be cool one day if they ever fix it.
Oliver, when's Subnautica below zero?
I said this just before Kanto, but probably after inscription.
You stream Starcraft?
Yeah, I do.
I play on the ladder, Starcraft 2.
You can still play Starcraft 2 blind.
No, you can't.
Trust me, that game is hard enough as it is with vision.
Yeah.
Actually, when I start Elden Ring, the first part of it is not going to be blind because I played the first six or so hours of it back when it came out.
So the very beginning area, I forgot the name of it, but I played that part, some of it at least.
But I was pretty slow, so I don't think I experienced too much of that first part, but yeah.
When I play it, I'll, of course, let you know where exactly or what I didn't expect.
But the thing is, it's an open world game.
Honestly, I don't really remember where I was and where I wasn't, you know?
Ixion.
It's a good game.
Involves building and surviving in space on a spaceship.
Yeah, I heard the Obsidian Ant talk about that, I think, in the past.
It was quite popular for a couple days, but then nobody's played it anymore or something.
But maybe it's just a short game.
Will you ever do a tier list of all the games you've played blind?
Well, that would be cool, actually.
Yeah, maybe one day.
But it would have to be after enough time, so I have enough games to have on the tier list, right?
I haven't played that many yet.
But I can give you a tier list right now for the best games I've ever played.
World of Warcraft, Starcraft 2.
Like, this is not even a competition for just the amount of time I spent on those two games.
And single-player games, probably Outer Wilds is up there.
For sure.
I'm trying to inject my friends with the About Oliver demon virus.
Oh, no.
It needs to become a saying.
The demon.
Tier list stream.
How about we do a tier list of tier lists?
You like roguelikes?
Risk of rain, Hades, things.
Yeah, I played Hades.
I fucking love that game.
I was in love with that.
That game is freaking fantastic.
I had so much fun with Hades.
Can't wait for the second one.
I want to see a demon.
I don't think we got to see a demon today, guys.
There's no demon today.
We don't do demon on Sunday.
Now that you're playing Inscription, how about Slay the Spire?
I think that's maybe on my list too.
Sure, I'll check it out.
So Inscription was a really big surprise.
I was expecting to like it, but not love it the way I do.
That game, I die a lot in that game, but I don't mind.
Because I just love starting over and building a new deck and shit.
It's so much fun.
Inscription is incredible.
Oh, 40 gold instead of 40 gold.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Hello, how are you?
Hey, Woots.
How you doing?
I'm very good, man.
I'm about to go outside and touch grass soon.
How about you?
How's life treating you in Sweden?
That's so great to hear I love Inscription so much.
Yeah, me too.
I've become a mega fan ever since I played it.
I wonder if...
Nah.
I just want more of it, you know?
I'm not even done with it yet, but I want more already.
It's so good.
Ah, green stuff.
It's good for brain.
Actually, it is.
Just walking around is good for the brain.
Pacing a bit.
Started with WoW again, so no grass touching for a while.
No, Woots.
Wait a minute.
What are you playing?
Is it the season of discovery or what?
It's gotta be, right?
Or is it the plunder thingy that everyone's talking about?
Like WoW ruined games for me.
It reprogrammed my brain to play a game like it was a job.
But it's so good, though.
It's such a good job.
It's the best job ever.
Kata is coming soon.
Ah, okay.
Yeah.
I see.
But do you really want to play Kata, though?
Like, really?
Isn't that why Classic was invented to begin with?
Because it started going downhill from there?
But maybe it's like different because...
It's about all the people starting together again, and it's the rush of, you know, starting over, you know?
I guess that's the fun part.
Are you pre-recording on the non-stream Let's Plays?
Am I pre-recording?
I don't know what you mean.
I am recording them.
Yeah.
I am recording...
I mean, oh, I think...
Yeah, I record quite a long time ahead.
So I have a bank of stuff to upload on the days where I can't play games.
I have frequent times when I can't play anything for a good chunk of time.
So then I have a library of stuff I can put up in the meanwhile.
Ah, yes, yes.
Hippogree.
Yes, the answer is yes.
I do.
They caught me at a weak moment.
I was bored and now I'm leveling my 19th character.
You know how it is.
Yeah.
Man, I just want classic again.
Like, let's start over.
Let's go again, you know?
Vanilla again.
One more time.
From the very beginning.
That's what I want.
Start over.
Fresh, exactly.
Super sunk cost, fallacy, and shadow lands for me.
I actually never played shadow lands, I think.
Maybe I did.
But very shortly, it was like, nah, that's not for me.
When will Oliver play Noiter?
I need my Noiter fix.
Probably someday.
Someday soon, maybe.
New to Terraria?
Yes, Eclipse.
This is my...
Actually, I think I'm at 60 hours or something.
But I still feel like quite the noob in this game.
I need Noiter injected into my abdomen.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Okay.
Well, it is your birthday, so I think you're allowed to do that sort of thing.
Did someone say fresh?
I don't know.
I think so.
Yeah, everybody wish Hive a happy birthday.
Well, I gotta go, dinner's ready, see y'all, have a good day.
Yeah, the Lord Eternal, I'll see you next time.
You better be there next time.
Or else, I will appear in front of your window with an industrial grade printer.
Okay, I'm out of here.
Thanks for stopping by, everybody.
Boots!
Good to see you, man.
We gotta play some games soon.
Anything.
Alright, bye-bye.